(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
Kazu will accept me.
I believe in him wholeheartedly, but...
I get scared.
Kazu, where do your true feelings lie?
Why?
How is Sayaka?
Here.
Do you know what caused this?
Not in the slightest.
Why would she...
I've been working hard for her sake.
Is the reason you've kept in touch
with Chie Hashimoto,
- also for Sayaka's sake?
- Huh?
How did you... Did I ever mention that?
You're free to stay.
I've been talking to her about Sayaka.
[Chie: I enjoyed our chat the other day!]
Chie is someone I can trust.
She's been a great person to confide in.
Seems like she had another agenda.
I happened to witness Chie and Airi
on my way back from a shoot the other night.
Thinking I could find another lead,
I decided to follow them.
Long time no see!
- So glad to see you're doing well.
- Sayaka?
That dress...
So that's who she went to see.
This is where things get complicated.
We wanted to ask you about Kazuomi.
You've never had any doubts about him?
Kazuomi invited me out
while you were bedridden.
He said he wanted to talk.
What?
He brought me to his place, held my hand,
and even tried to kiss me.
What?
You're the one who wanted to read my palm.
He calls me to ask for "advice",
- and complains about you.
- Unbelievable.
Sayaka, I'm just worried about you.
I want you to be happy.
I really didn't want to say this, but...
I'm going to be blunt for your sake, okay?
I think you should leave him.
What?
That man's a cheater.
You're better off without him!
Me?
A cheater?
This is the person you've "trusted".
She's the worst.
What is with this woman?
Chie Hashimoto can't stand being inferior.
She especially seems to compare
her happiness to Sayaka's.
In other words?
She hoped to drag Sayaka out of marriage,
and back down to her level.
I thought she was a good person.
I never thought she'd be such a villain.
You make that sort of judgement often.
"They're good", "they're bad".
But your evaluation changes often.
Well, yeah.
That's on people for changing.
Is it really?
You've interpreted both the "good" and "bad"
in ways that would justify your actions.
Even your own "good intentions"
can be misconstrued by Sayaka.
You had met Chie Hashimoto in secrecy,
while Sayaka was bedridden in the hospital.
But that was because...
Sayaka then sees her husband
receive an intimate text from her friend.
I went to ask her about Sayaka.
Her husband begins returning home late.
How do you think she would interpret
this situation?
Well, when you put it like that...
You're an earnest man, Hayashida.
But being earnest and naive
are two sides of the same coin.
Good people. Bad people.
You can't judge a person's true nature
if you only have two extremes.
A person's true nature...
If you only see things on a surface level,
you'll eventually make
an irredeemable mistake.
Don't you realize your actions till now
have caused Sayaka an immense amount of pain?
Sayaka was driven to suicide because...
Everything I've done was for Sayaka's sake.
And yet... How am I supposed to face her now?
You're awake.
I went and spoke to the doctor.
They said you'll be discharged tomorrow.
Kazu.
You must be angry.
I made a rash decision.
I'm not angry.
Was there anything you wanted from the store?
Kazuomi?
Hey, Kazuomi.
Kazuomi.
I'm sorry I ran my mouth about your wedding.
It's fine.
It's not fine.
This was supposed to be
a big moment for you two.
And I totally rained on your parade.
I'm really sorry about what I did.
Let's put that behind us already.
Why're you here on a weekday anyway?
Are you feeling ill?
No. My mother wasn't feeling too well.
Is she okay?
Yeah. Why're you here?
[Makoto Sugiura: Ryokusei Pharmaceutical]
I'm here on business.
Do you know a doctor,
or someone who's well versed in medicines?
They could help us identify
this ulcer-triggering drug.
What?
Are there any drugs
that can affect your stomach?
That's a broad question.
What about a drug that triggers an ulcer?
I mean, it can be a potential side effect.
What about something
that triggers the effect instantly?
A sudden ulcer, huh?
I can't think of anything
that specifically targets the stomach.
Why ask?
I was just curious.
Then what about a drug
that turns blue when dissolved?
It's a question that's been on my mind.
Because, you know.
I was curious.
There is a medicine
that turns water blue when dissolved.
It's a type of sleeping pill.
A sleeping pill?
I've never heard of one
that changes the color of water.
It was a recent invention.
You know, with the rise of people
using sleeping pills for no good.
So people can instantly tell
if their drink has been spiked.
Bingo.
Is that why...
The culprit mixed it into her blue champagne?
Not all sleeping pills
have that effect, though.
Say, are you free after this?
Huh?
Let me treat you to a drink or two.
I want to make it up to you somehow.
- Evening.
- Welcome.
Could I get the usual?
Of course.
I'll have a whisky.
Coming right up.
Here. Cheers.
If Sayaka was only put to sleep,
does that mean the culprit
had no intent on killing her?
But then why...
You were asking about pills
because of the wedding, right?
What?
You suck at making excuses.
So Sayaka was drugged.
Don't worry, I promise I won't tell a soul.
But I've never heard of a sleeping pill
that'd cause an ulcer.
If that's true...
Sayaka?
Then why did she choke out blood?
- Sayaka!
Was it the stress and anxiety
that came from playing the violin?
She was already drowsy
from whatever she was drugged with.
Did her added stress cause the ulcer?
What?
I still can't believe the bride herself
wrecked her own wedding.
The gal's a bundle of misfortune, I tell you.
Bundle of misfortune?
And here I thought she'd be happy with you.
I can already see her breaking down again.
Does Sayaka know about the drugging?
Why are you acting so familiar with her?
Am I?
Sorry, blame it on the alcohol.
What do you mean breaking down, "again"?
She's talked to me about her episodes before.
I thought Sayaka was a friend of a friend.
My bad. Didn't mean to fuel the flame.
Just forget it, yeah?
That's not happening.
What aren't you telling me?
Nothing, nothing.
This is how you behave whenever you lie.
What was your relationship to Sayaka?
Look me in the eyes, damn it.
Yeesh, you're such a buzzkill.
I was dating her.
When?
We broke up before I introduced you to her.
Wait, but weren't you...
Yeah, I was already dating my wife.
Then you were...
Two-timing them? Yeah.
What's with that look, man?
It's not that unheard of.
That's why I called Sayaka
a "friend of a friend".
Sorry for lying.
She's actually a girl I met on a dating app.
A dating app famous for hookups and flings.
But you wouldn't have given Sayaka
the time of day if I told you that.
So I kept some details under wraps.
I wanted you two to tie the knot, after all.
If I'm being honest,
Sayaka and I were only friends with benefits.
Friends with benefits.
Hope that shared experience
doesn't bother you.
Shared experience.
Eventually, my actual girlfriend got pregnant,
so I took responsibility and married her.
Sayaka and I would break up,
and that'd be that.
Except, she became insane
when I asked to end things.
She'd send me letters
when I blocked her number,
and followed me everywhere. Creepy, huh?
Your infidelity is the real issue here.
Hey, woah. Sayaka's not any better than me.
You know how her mother is, right?
Maybe she needed to rebel to feel in control,
but Sayaka really went wild
when she left the nest.
I bet I wasn't her only "friend".
Of course, I pitied her home situation.
But her persistence
wasn't making it any easier on me.
And that's when you came into the picture.
You pushed a woman onto me,
because you didn't need her anymore?
Hey, I'm the reason you're married at all.
No need to be so harsh, yeah?
Besides, I set you two up...
For Sayaka's sake, too.
How?
How does this benefit Sayaka at all?
I felt bad leaving her single
while I got married.
Huh?
I know I ended up dumping her.
But I did like her quite a bit.
Quite a bit?
Yeah, I cherished her.
I felt responsible when we broke up.
It really broke my heart saying goodbye.
Quit talking like you know it all!
Hey, I'm telling the truth here.
Sayaka said you weren't a bad option either.
And what do you know? It was a success.
All's well that ends well, right?
Quit acting like you've summarized anything.
You must've felt so relieved
when I told you I wanted to date Sayaka.
How could you attend the wedding
with a straight face?
You used to date the bride, for god's sake.
What're you getting so heated for?
You think you're so innocent yourself?
I know you're no better.
Don't even try to lump us together.
I'm glad Sayaka didn't marry
a scumbag like you.
I thought Makoto was a dear friend of mine.
Since when did his personality
get so twisted?
He used to be such a good guy.
Good people. Bad people.
You can't judge a person's true nature
if you only have two extremes.
I am nothing like Makoto.
Sayaka is my wife.
I'm the only one who can protect her.
Sayaka.
I love Sayaka.
I'll be the one to make her happy.
A drug that turns liquids blue.
[Kazuomi Hayashida]
Okay, let's say Sayaka was drugged
with a sleeping pill.
We're ready.
It's possible to acquire such a pill
if Sayaka was diagnosed with insomnia.
But why use a drug
that would turn any liquid blue?
Were they unaware of other,
non-color changing sleeping pills?
Or was the one thing they acquired,
this color-changing drug?
In order to disguise this change in color,
the culprit would have to know
blue champagne was on the menu.
[Concerto]
Someone like the bride's mother,
Kaori Wakamatsu, for example.